And lo and behold, it
was the right choice.
Had I not spilled that fateful
cup of coffee, where would I be?
No way!
It's not possible!
It was supposed to work out!
Brat!
So you poked your nose around
and found Stray Cat, huh?!
Oh, I bother.
As long as I keep Bites
the Dust activated,
it'll function to keep my secret
and protect you at all cost.
Crap! I blew it!
And the others don't have
long before they get blown up!
You tried to end me once and for all with
one of Stray Cat's
compressed air projectiles.
Hayato,
there's no way your little pea brain
could have come up with such a clever
idea unless you'd already experienced
this morning at least three or four times.
The fact that you've lived through
this morning that many times?
Is a surefire sign that bites the dust
is destined to eradicate not just Rohan?
but at least one of
his companions as well.
So your loose lips won't only sink Rohan,
but whichever one of his
friends you ran your mouth to.
Did the would-be
detectives gang up on you?
Who have you murdered this time?
Well, was it a runt by the name of Koichi?
Or maybe it was Jotaro Kujo.
Knowing that he's dead would make
this a red-letter day indeed.
It's all over!
It'd be far too risky for me to allow
you to relive any more of this morning.
That would expose me to an attack.
So once the others die, I'll
temporarily disengage Bites the Dust.
Bites the Dust is all-powerful!
It took a while, but luck is
finally on Yoshikage Kira's side.
Wait a second.
That name, Kira, is that your real...
Huh?
Whoopsie.
Did I just reveal my true
name to you by mistake?
Indeed.
I'm none other than Yoshikage Kira.
You can shout it to the
heavens if it suits your fancy.
By the way, do you have the time?
You're dead wrong I haven't mentioned
you to anyone I never opened my mouth to!
Anyone because I knew exactly what would
happen to them if I did so instead I
decided to make a call I remembered he
said he overslept and was running late
so I found his number and woke him up
I didn't break any rules I just phoned
a friend and remember one thing you're
the one who revealed his own secret?
identity.
I was just stalling for
a bit of extra time.
Time for him to drag himself out of
bed and show up a little earlier.
Breakdown! Breakdown!
Night to night,
night is my
Night to night, night is my soul?
Breakdown, Breakdown!
Hey, Josuke!
Looks like we're gonna make it to
the big meeting on Time After All!
Hold it! No.
This guy, he isn't who he says he is.
I don't know if it was pure
chance or fate giving us a break?
but I heard this guy say a certain name.
I don't believe it.
Believe it, asshole, cause I know I just
heard you say the name Yoshikage Kira.
Seriously?
What are the chances?
This isn't chance.
It's not fate either.
This was making a gamble and
lucky for me it paid off.
Your end has arrived.
Just admit it already.
I know I heard the name
slither out of your mouth.
It can't be!
Murderer!
If it turns out you and him just happened
to share a name, don't you worry.
I can heal if need be.
This bastard's really Yoshikage Kira?
Damn that little brat.
I should have known he
would lead me to ruin.
This can't be happening.
I have to deactivate Bites the Dust so
I can defend myself from these cretins!
Protect me, Deadly Queen!
It's chilly.
Must be due to all this rain.
Really, is it too much to ask for
certain people to show up on time?
Oh, there's Koichi and Jotaro.
All right!
I beat the clock!
I defeated destiny!
I was never one for rapturous hives. No,
so long as I avoided dispiriting loads,
I was content to live
as carefree as a daisy.
More than anything, I sought to live
a quiet life of peace and tranquility.
You've finally shown yourself!
That'll make it real easy to knock that
peace and tranquility
right off your new face!
Whoa, it's the dude from Rohan's picture!
I would've guessed we'd end
up meeting the guy here!
I'm pretty sure we didn't run
into him by chance, Okuyasu.
I haven't figured out all of it,
but given that he revealed his
real name to Hayato Kawajiri,
I get the feeling we showed
up just in the nick of time.
Before you dullards get
all high and mighty,
I should tell you I wasn't
running away despite appearances.
I can obliterate any one of you the
instant the thought occurs to me.
I detest conflict.
I hate the very idea of it with the
white-hot intensity of a thousand suns.
Conflict runs completely
counter to the peace
and tranquility I strive
for every day of my life.
It's really quite simple to rise
victorious in a single battle.
But, of course, the stress begins
to pile up before the next one.
It's a foolish endeavor.
To engage in conflict is
to engage in futility.
You brought this shit on yourself when
you murdered Shigetsu, you frickin' idiot!
You're a sick son of a
bitch who kills for fun!
You shouldn't get the privilege of flapping
those stolen gums, you cat-eyed freak!
Watch yourself, Josuke!
Make sure you avoid Deadly Queen's
creepy bomb hand at all costs.
I've already told you the reason for
my not obliterating all of you earlier.
The only souls standing between me and my
eternal peace and
tranquility are you three.
Since I've been found out, I have
no choice but to do battle with you.
Things are about to get dicey,
Hayato, so get behind us now!
Let's see now.
Shining Diamond's range
is one to two meters.
And it corrects that which
has been destroyed or altered.
I won't be fixin' you up, buddy,
so don't even worry about it!
A good ass-kicking's the only
treatment you're getting!
Hey, look out!
Dora.
He's tough.
I can't tell what happened,
but Kira hacking up blood and flying
through the air gets a hell yeah from me!
Your deadly queen's as slow as molasses.
For all the killing you do,
you're a real lethargic fighter.
Guess all that peace and
tranquility will do that to ya.
It's painfully obvious that your stand
just isn't cut out for one-on-one fighting.
Jousuke, he's slow, but
don't let your guard down!
If you wanna knock him around
without laying a finger on him,
there's no better stand to have
on your side than the hand!
Bring it!
You scrape away space
to transport things, eh?
Josuke was my target, but it appears fate
has other ideas in mind for me today.
I'm now poised to attack you.
I know, I'll use the Plat!
What?
Nice, direct hit.
That wasn't too bad.
Especially for beginners, luck.
What the hell happened?
I didn't see anything. Touch me.
It's the air. The air.
Spit some kind of fire.
Okuyasu.
Did I hear him right?
The air spit fire.
But how?
Well, boys.
Do you see?
Now this is why I kept my pet.
I've found a way to use Stray Cat's air
-controlling abilities in
Deadly Queen's explosions.
I must thank you for carting
it all the way here, Hayato.
The invisibility of the air mixed
with the power of an explosion.
He couldn't have used a more dangerous
combination of elements if he tried.
He was growing it to do this all along.
And I'm the wise guy who brought
the stupid thing right to him.
I did tell you luck was
finally on my side, didn't I?
But the characters that make up
the word luck are bringing life.
How deliciously apropos.
Is something wrong, Mr. Jotaro?
No, it's nothing.
For a moment I thought I heard Josuke,
but I guess it was just the rain.
Quintessential Josuke, I'm
sure the slob overslept again.
If he's not here in five minutes flat,
I'm going straight to
Hayato Kawajiri's school?
and I'll leave you two here
to wait for everyone else.
I'm gonna make you as
good as new, Okuyasu!
That's certainly a noble thought.
But you see, it's time for you to explode.
That cat plant launched
air at him like a bullet!
It can transform air into an explosive!
Here it is!
You've got to run now!
You can't see it!
It's that weird bubble thing!
Move!
It's gonna get you!
Oh, that's right!
He has the power to fix things,
which means he can heal Okuyasu!
To fix that which is broken,
using your power to reassemble broken
stone into a wall was impressive.
I've got it again!
Kay, it's coming!
Nothing in the world is as terrifying?
As the act of assumption!
Especially for those contemptible few!
Who assume the false superiority.
of their own talents
and special abilities.
Yo, it's squeezing through!
Contact it and cause it to explode!
I thought it would at
least decapitate him.
But lucky for him, the destructive
force was rather shallow.
My deadly queen's explosion is not
limited to objects it directly touches.
Thinking so was an assumption.
It can generate an explosion
at any distance I wish.
No matter where you try
to hide or how quickly
you build a protective
stone wall or metal plate,
my bomb will slip through any
obstacle and execute its target.
You won't escape with your life this time.
Now die.
It's no use.
There's no way to dodge it.
What do you mean, dodge it?
I have no intention of escaping.
For the record, I would never run away.
How else would I heal Okuyasu's wounds?
He's charging right into it.
It went around him!
I thought you said you could
detonate that thing at any distance.
I must have found the exception.
Namely, I'm just a little too close for
comfort for you to try blowing me up.
Doing that wouldn't end
well for you now, would it?
Alright, hang on.
I'll have you healed before you know it.
You can't touch him!
Trust me on this!
If I know Kira, he's
already transformed Okuyasu!
He's a bomb!
Damn that little whelp. He what? No!
I never saw Deadly Queen lay
even a finger on Okuyasu!
What makes you think he
was able to pull that off?
You're not a stand user,
so how would you know?
I just do!
I've lived in the same house as
that psycho until this morning!
His face tells me everything!
His stand touched him
before we could notice!
Josuke, please!
You gotta trust me!
Okuyasu's a bomb now!
Yoshikage Kira!
Easy.
Give me a moment to think.
Well, now. Let's see.
You stormed at me out of the blue,
so I can't really say
whether I touched him or not.
Actually, the whole
incident was such a blur.
Perhaps I should press
the switch and find out.
No! Please don't!
I'm begging you!
Just hurry up and shoot
your next air missile!
Point the damn thing at me and shoot!
Come on! Do it!
Really, now, there's no need to be hasty
and end the fun so quickly, is there?
Josuke Higashikata,
I think I'll observe you
a little while longer
and then decide if I
should obliterate you.
Besides, you honestly have no real proof
I turned Okuyasu into a bomb at all.
It might be possible to heal
him with Shining Diamond.
I could be overstepping here,
but at this point it
would appear you have only
one course of action if
you want to save Okuyasu.
You must heal him by way of touching him.
I don't envy the position you're in.
If he is a human bomb,
touching him with Shining
Diamond may kill you,
but Okuyasu would be spared the
fate of exploding into oblivion.
If you heal your dear
friend's critical injuries,
at least your sacrifice
won't have been in vain.
No!
Don't touch him, Josuke!
I'll wait until you've made your decision.
Do you save your best friend's life?
Or do you just attack me and let him die?
Wow.
I'm content to wait until
you make a decision.
But it seems you're averse
to touching your friend,
even when it means keeping him alive.
I have proof touching him is deadly!
I know for a fact that Kira's only
able to control one bomb at a time.
Once he's activated one
of his freaky bomb things,
it's impossible for him to fire off the
next one until the first has been detonated.
Think about it.
He only used one at a time.
Why wouldn't he launch a bunch at once?
He's made Okuyasu into a
bomb so he can't shoot now.
Are you trying to make a point?
The point is there's still a way to save
Okuyasu, but someone needs to touch him.
Hmm?
Deadly Queen, bomb switch on!
And that someone has gotta be me!
Hayato!
Now I get it!
Shining Diamond!
You're one crazy-ass SOB, Hayato.
Took some major balls to
set off the bomb like that.
You sure you're a grade School?
Because that was Bites.
Yeah, well, I couldn't
stand around doing nothing,
and I knew you had the power to heal me.
I refuse to let any more
innocent people die.
Besides, if you're gone, he'll
off me in the blink of an eye,
and he'll be free to do whatever he wants.
It's just a matter of time
before he kills my mom,
and then he'll go after
more people in this town.
But first, you die, though your
power is certainly an issue.
To think your stand can reverse my
destructive acts in mere seconds.
I'd almost forgotten
how much that annoying
healing ability of yours vexes me utterly.
Deadly Queen!
Josuke, he's gonna shoot!
It'll detonate on impact so you'll have
no opportunity to guard. Then again,
you could sidestep the explosive
if you happen to see it,
So I've launched one so small
it's almost impossible to detect.
With Okuyasu on your back and
those painful shrapnel wounds,
can you really dodge a projectile?
Just get the hell out of there, Josuke!
If the explosion so much as brushes
against you, you'll be a dead man!
I healed you!
Why haven't you woken up yet?
Open those beady eyes, Okuyasu!
The bomb's on its way!
Move it!
Only eight more meters until impact.
All right, enough goofing around, buddy.
It's time to wake up now.
You're as good as new, Okuyasu!
Chusuke, please!
Seven meters to go.
Don't you leave me, dick!
Open your damn eyes! Hey!
Come on, man, quit napping and
open your freaking eyes! Hey,
if you wake up, we can knock the shit out
of this asshole just like we always do!
Chusuke, go!
Like joe montana throwing the
touchdown pass of a winning game,
i'll detonate the sucker
in the perfect position.
and go home victorious.
Four meters until impact.
Go! Right now!
You've gotta run for it or
it's gonna hit you dead on!
I'm so sorry about Okuyasu,
but he's already...
No, don't say it!
The only one of us who needs
to run here is you, kid!
Two meters till showtime.
With a three meter radius, they're
sure to die in the explosion.
I can see it!
It's two meters in front of
you and it's closing in fast!
You've gotta run now!
Listen to me, Josuke!
Okuyasu's gone! He's dead!
Accept it already!
He's nowhere near dead, dammit!
He's back in top form and he'll
open his eyes any minute now!
Yes, just one more meter and then
pop goes the riff-raff. Josuke!
Holy heck!
It was ruptured by a blade of blood!
Did Josuke somehow take
his blood and propel
it with so much force
that it cut like a knife?
Oh, yeah.
It's just like that time in the attic.
The air shackles deflated when I
punctured them with a compass needle.
He used the blood from his wound
like a water jet cutter. Hmph.
And he severed the bullet clean through.
Nice try, but it didn't do you any good.
You gotta move!
They didn't deflate!
This improvised air bullet explosive
is stabilized by Deadly Queen,
so it won't deflate.
You can split it, smash
it, or dice it to pieces.
But I'm pleased to say the
bomb will never lose its power.
And now, back to our
regularly scheduled explosion.
Touchdown.
What the heck's going on?
He's floating?
Explode.
No, this isn't floating!
Shining Diamond won't
allow me to heal myself,
which, to be frank, would
come in handy right now.
But when it comes to pieces of road,
like the ones that got lodged
in me from the first blast,
that's a whole different story.
What a super neat idea, using
the road to pull you up.
I'm out of options.
You don't live here, but it'll
work as our safe house for now.
Please, you have to leave Okuyasu.
If you keep carrying him
around, you're gonna get killed.
He'll find a way to corner
you, and that'll be it!
I asked you to keep quiet, so drop it!
Okuyasu and I have a connection.
He's my friend.
I won't abandon him.
No, that's not what I'm trying to say!
By the time you healed
Okuyasu, he was already dead!
Enough!
Enough.
Not another word. I mean it.
You've got to focus your
energy on beating Kira!
How irksome.
That blasted ability to correct.
Without it, my bomb would be unstoppable.
I see now that the greatest
obstacle standing in the
way of my attaining peace
and tranquility isn't Jotaro.
It's him.
Josuke Higashikata.
I want you, but I don't know if I
need you, but I'm trying to find you.